Guide to the Peninsula-Times Tribune Photographs of Stanford University PC0065
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photographs, 1959-1992
  - United Stanford Workers (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Non-Stanford images (Box 8, Folder 12)